Finding Aid for the Kay Sugahara Papers LSC.2354
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Series 2: Trip files, 1968-1988
  - Will. J. Donovan Dinner honoring Reagan, 1986 May 29 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Governors Association, 1982 February 18-23 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Response to KS speech on $100 bill. loan, 1982 March (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Wanda Urbanska, NY visit, 1983 August (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - VSS Thailand Trip, 1986 postponed to 1987, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Saudi Arabian Trip, 1975 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Japan Trip, 1977 September-November (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Japan Trip, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - KS China Trip, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 2-5)
  - Trip Files - SF, Hawaii, Tokyo, Sendai, NY, 1983 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - UCLA trip file, 1983 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - China trip, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 7-9)
  - Japan trip, 1981 September (Box 71, Folder 10-11)
  - Guam, Honolulu, LA, 1981 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Trip file Marco Is., Tampa, Tallahassee, 1982 January (Box 75, Folder 8-9)
  - Jamaica trip, 1981 (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - KS - Washington trip file, 1982 (Box 75, Folder 11-13)
  - KS - Washington trip file, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 1-6)
  - H. Shimanouchi visit to the US, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - KS - LA trip USAI seminar, 1982 May (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - KS - Wash. trip file - Brock mtg., press luncheon, 1982 May 18 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Tokyo trip files, 1982 (Box 76, Folder 10-17)
  - Washington trips, 1982 August-September (Box 76, Folder 18-20)
  - USAI - Ill. Issue Forum, 1982 September (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - KS - SF, Chicago, Wash. trip, 1982 September-October (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - KS - Trip folder: Univ. of Ark., SF, Carmel, NY, 1982 December 26 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - VSS Reception for Prince Bernhardt of the Netherlands, Wash. DC, 1982 October 7 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - KS Washington trip, 1981 January 12-13 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - Nigeria trip, 1981 February 13 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Jamaica trip - KS & YS, 1981 April 3-7 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - HTS visit to NY, 1981 June (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Nigerian luncheon - Washington, Metropolitan Club, 1981 May 7 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Craig Spence dinner - D.C., 1981 June 29 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Trip file - D.C., 1981 May 14 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Mexico trip File, 1981 July 7-10 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - DC trip - USAI Open House, 1981 July 27-28 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Trip File - Wash., S.F., Guam, Hawaii, LA, Las Vegas, NY, 1981 October 27-December 10 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - KS - Tokyo trip file, 1983 November (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - KS Speech - USAI Western Conf., L.A, 1983 November (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - KS Speech Fulbright Alumni Assoc. Meeting, 1983 September 23-25 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Trip file - Nisei Festival, LA, 1983 August 9-16 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - David Kamerman 90th Birthday Ceremony, 1983 August (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - VSS Dinner honoring Stephensen - USS Intrepid, 1983 September (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - Trip file - SF Board meetings, 1983 September 25-October 2 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - KS - Tokyo trip, 1982 November 1-24 (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - KS - NY, SF, Tokyo, China, Hong Kong, 1981 August 26-September 25 (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - VSS - Donovan Foundation, 1985-1986 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - Governor Spellman dinner, 1984 July 31 (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - VSS - Donovan Foundation Symposium, 1985 November (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Whittier College Nixon Scholar, 1984-1985 (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Washington DC - USAI Conference, 1986 February 17-22 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - St. Croix, 1986 February (Box 78, Folder 6-7)
  - Speeches - KS, 1980-1983 (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - LA Trip - UCLA Award and USAI Western, 1983 June 2-6 (Box 78, Folder 9)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Yano Trip - Bermuda, 1983 June 6-18 (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Augusta Georgia trip - Masters course, 1983 May 6-8 (Box 78, Folder 11)
  - Nakasone Dinner Japan Society, 1983 May (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - Speech PIP LA, 1982 May 3 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Speech Chicago USAI, 1982 September (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Japan trip, 1983 March (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - USAI Speech, 1983 April (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Third Ann. Conference USAI DC, 1983 April 21-23 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - Fulbright Alumni Association meeting, 1985 October 11-12 (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Las Vegas trip, 1985 June 25-26 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Presidential Inauguration trip, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 18-19)
  - Whittier College trip files, 1985 April (Box 80, Folder 1-2)
  - Golf Trip - Eastern Seniors, 1985 March 17-21 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - St. Croix vacation, 1985 February (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - KS trip file schedule, 1984 October 4-November 29 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - M. O'Connell Wedding, 1984 September (Box 80, Folder 6)
  - Lee Elder Golf, 1984 October (Box 80, Folder 7)
  - Washington trip - Eagles - President, 1984 January 26 (Box 80, Folder 8)
  - Florida trip, 1984 February 17-27 (Box 80, Folder 9)
  - Washington trip, 1984 May (Box 80, Folder 10)
  - USAI trip file, 1984 June 17-19 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Speech Chicago USAI, 1982 September 28 (Box 80, Folder 12)
  - H. Shimanouchi trip to US, 1984 June (Box 80, Folder 13)
  - Tokyo trip folders, 1980 (Box 89, Folder 3-4)
  - Las Vegas, 1980 (Box 91, Folder 4)
  - Trip to Cleveland, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - For NY, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - Trip file Tokyo, 1980 April (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - Asian American - NY, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - Ecuador trip, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - Greece trip, 1980 (Box 94, Folder 8-9)
  - Florida trip, 1980 August (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - AMC trip, 1980 July (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - Tokyo trip, 1980 August (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - White House trip, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - LA trip file, 1980 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Japan trip, 1980 November (Box 95, Folder 4)
  - Elf Christening, 1981 March (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - Jolly Sprite Christening, 1981 February (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - San Francisco trip, 1981 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - Min. Kumagai, Jap. Embassy DC, 1986 (Box 103, Folder 5)
  - KS trip file - Japan, 1986 October-November (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - KS trip file - China, 1986-1988 (Box 110, Folder 6)
  - KS trip file - Tokyo, Thailand, 1987 October-November (Box 125, Folder 1-2)
  - Trip file Tokyo, 1986 September-November (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Trip file - St Croix, 1988 (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Trip file - LA/Tokyo/St/Croix, 1987 March (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Guest List - Tokyo dinner to honor VP Mondale, 1981 November 26 (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Bermuda trip file - KS - YS - Ty Ralli, 1988 July 6-8 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Trip file - Maine vacation, 1987 August 17-21 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Tokyo schedules, 1985 June, 1986 September-October (Box 126, Folder 5-6)
  - KS trip reports, 1980-1984 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - Tokyo - Thailand trip files, 1987 (Box 126, Folder 11-12)
  - Trip notebooks, 1982-1987 (Box 130, Folder 8-14)
  - Trip notebooks, 1972-1982 (Box 131, Folder 5-19)
  - Trip notebooks, 1973-1978 (Box 132, Folder 6-16)
  - Tokyo tape transcripts, 1973 (Box 156, Folder 2)
  - KS Japan trip files, 1975-1978 (Box 189, Folder 20-23)
  - KS California trip, 1979 (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - Japan trip, 1978 (Box 195, Folder 8)
  - KS Houston, 1979 (Box 195, Folder 9)
  - KS Paris & London, 1978 (Box 195, Folder 10)
  - Florida trip, 1980 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Japan trip, 1980 (Box 200, Folder 5)
- Series 3: Personal files, 1928-1988
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  SERIES CONTAINS AUDIO AND AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: This series contains both processed and unprocessed audio and audiovisual materials. For information about the access status of the material that you are looking for, refer to the Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements note at the file levels. All requests to access processed audio and audiovisual materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  The personal files include scrapbooks, photo albums, correspondence, diaries, appointment books, documentation of Granada, Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) reports, biographical manuscripts, awards, audio, audiovisual, and press materials.
  - Newspaper clippings KS obituary, 1988 September (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - KS obituary clippings foreign and domestic, 1988 September (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - KS Congressman Torricelli's Tribute to Kay Sugahara in CR, 1988 October 5 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - KS Flowers and cards received at hospital and funeral, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Tozai Times, Teru Kanazawa article, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Nisei Week - Rafu Shirnpo article, 1983 August 16 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Nisei Week, LA Herald article, 1983 August 11 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - National Geographic, KS article, 1986 April (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - National Geographic entire issue, 1986 April (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - PIP, Los Angeles Times article, 1982 February 19 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - PIP Washington Post article, 1982 February 19 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - KS - Liz Nakahara's article Washington Post, 1981 October 8 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Newsweek article - Japanese Marshall Plan, 1982 March 1 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Tristen Beplat article - Nippon Kenzai Shimbun, 1983 January (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - AP article, Newark Star Ledger, 1983 January 10 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - AP article, Honolulu Star Bulletin PIP, 1983 January 9 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - API article by Steve Wilson - Japan Times, 1982 December 26 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Yukio Ozaki: Memorial Foundation - Mrs. Yukika Sohma, Daughter brochures, 1982 April 1 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - PIP - Japan Times articles, 1982 July 24 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - PIP - Mainichi Daily News article, 1982 July 22 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - PIP - Rafu article, 1982 July 22 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Newspaper articles, KS Guam visit, 1981 November (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Extra copies, PIP clippings - USAI, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - KS - USAI Bill Hosokawa clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Nisei Week Festival magazine - KS Grand Marshall, 1983 August (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Nisei Week - LA Herald Examiner - W. Urbanska article, 1983 August (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Reagan - Nakasone dinner photos, 1987 May (Box 3, Folder 7-8)
  - FBI and CIA FOIA reports, 1984-1987 (Box 3, Folder 11-19)
  - CIA FOIA reports section A-D, 1986 August (Box 4, Folder 1-3)
  - KS clippings, circa 1970s (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Letters to/from Senators - MacKay, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Frank J. Fahrenkopf dinner photo album, 1985 November 19 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - St. Marcet II photo album, circa 1974 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Otaru Rex Oahu Rex photo album, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Conoco Canada, circa 1973 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - St. Marcet I photo album, circa 1974 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Sugahara Income Tax Returns, 1969-1974 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - KS personal, 1972-1977 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - KS taxes, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - KS personal, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Receipts, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - KS Social Security, 1978 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Receipts, 1980 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - K. Sugahara Personal, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - KS Social Security, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - KS personal, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - KS personal, 1982 (Box 67, Folder 12)
  - FEC 230, James Kauffman article, 1984 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - KS overseas data sheet photocopies, circa 1980s (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Dodo novel and correspondence, 1987 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Kay Sugahara Historical records, 1945-1955 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - Inner Circle Productions - Maria Elena Cellino, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Etsuko Steinmetz - Japanese school, CA, 1985 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Kurio, Howard and Greg, 1985-1986 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Tozai Times, Teru Kanazawa article, 1985 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - A Time for Daring - OSS TV project, 1979 (Box 85, Folder 10)
  - Prof. Schonberger Dooman book materials, 1945-1990 (Box 99, Folder 1-8)
  - KS file copies sent to Schonberger, 1990 July 19 (Box 100, Folder 1-7)
  - KS file copies sent to Schonberger, 1990 July 3 (Box 101, Folder 1-3)
  - Re: Japanese award to KS, 1985 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - KS biography, 1982 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - M. O'Connell interview transcriptions, 1982 February (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - Eastern Seniors Golf, 1985-1988 (Box 102, Folder 8)
  - Personal, 1985-1988 (Box 103, Folder 4)
  - Pelham Country Club, 1983-1988 (Box 103, Folder 10)
  - Sugahara biography draft, 1988 (Box 104, Folder 16)
  - Draft - Kleiner mss - KS biog., 1988 (Box 105, Folder 1-5)
  - Maria Machado - KS bio., 1985 (Box 105, Folder 6)
  - Kleiner bio - first draft, 1988 April 25 (Box 105, Folder 7)
  - Maria Machado - KS bio. files, 1986-1988 (Box 106, Folder 1-4)
  - Photographs - Fulbright Alumni Assoc. 40th Anniversary, 1986 September 12 (Box 106, Folder 5)
  - KS Portrait - by Bachrach, 1973 (Box 106, Folder 6)
  - Photographs - US Asia Reception, Washington DC, 1984 June 18 (Box 106, Folder 7)
  - YS & KS on yacht with Adnan Khashoggi, 1985 March 15 (Box 106, Folder 8)
  - Photographs - Flower arrangement in office, 1988 June (Box 106, Folder 9)
  - Photographs - Bermuda Trip with Mr. & Mrs. Ty Ralli, 1988 July 6-8 (Box 106, Folder 10)
  - Photographs - VSS dinner for Prime Minister Margaret Thatcher & Luncheon at Nippon Club for Mexican visitors to FML, 1981 February 28 (Box 107, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - policy study group Tokyo, 1981 (Box 107, Folder 2)
  - Photographs - USAI 3 day conference in DC, 1981 October (Box 107, Folder 3-5)
  - Photographs - Luncheon at Nippon Club honoring MP Motoo Shina, 1985 September (Box 107, Folder 6)
  - Photographs - USAI Conference Washington DC, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 7)
  - Photographs - VSS Dinner honoring President Reagan, 1986 (Box 107, Folder 8-9)
  - Photographs - Thwaites Inn - 50th Wedding Anniversary, 1985 May (Box 108, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - Whittier College, KS Nixon Scholar & visit to Las Vegas to Wayne Newton's home, 1985 April-May (Box 108, Folder 2)
  - Photocopies of dinner party photographs, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 3)
  - Photographs - UCLA Award to KS, 1983 June 4 (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - Photographs - Bermuda Trip with the Yanos, 1983 June (Box 108, Folder 5)
  - Photographs - Masters golf trip, 1983 May (Box 108, Folder 6)
  - Photographs - VSS Dinner honoring Stephenson; Golf - NJ, 1983 September 22 (Box 108, Folder 7)
  - Photographs - National Governors Conference, 1982 February 22 (Box 108, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous photos, 1981, 1984 (Box 108, Folder 9-10)
  - Photographs - Nigerian Prime Minister visit to NY, undated (Box 108, Folder 11)
  - Golf photographs - KS/FMK Bob Bruno/Steve Seig, 1980 October (Box 108, Folder 12)
  - Photographs - Jolly Sprite christening in Japan, 1981 February 26 (Box 108, Folder 13)
  - Photographs - Japan Society dinner & Donovan dinner, 1983 May (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Photographs - AMC, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 2)
  - Photographs - Greece Trip - President Carter, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 3)
  - Photographs - KS & YS guests of Jimmy Carter, 1980 June 17 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, 1980 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Photographs - Mr. and Mrs. Kato in Florida with KS & YS, 1983 (Box 109, Folder 6)
  - Photographs - Japan Line party - Tokyo, 1972 November 29 (Box 109, Folder 7)
  - Nakasone letters to KS, 1983-1987 (Box 109, Folder 9)
  - Golf Essays - Written for Tokyo Golf, 1988 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Prime Minister Nakasone - personal letters, 1986-1987 (Box 111, Folder 9-10)
  - Personal VIP diplomatic letters, 1947-1971 (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - KS - desk notebook, 1972-1973, 1978 (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence, 1960s (Box 124, Folder 11)
  - Claim for return of property, 1947-1949 (Box 124, Folder 12)
  - Kleiner correspondence, 1987 (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Nigeria certificate, 1980 (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Birth and marriage certificates, 1951-1974 (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - Japan bank accounts, undated (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - KS award file, 1985 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Esther Crane Kelser, 1982 (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Asian Wall Street Journal article, 1981 (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Photocopies of correspondence, 1940s-1980s (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Japanese award documentation, 1968 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Photocopies of ephemera, 1940s-1980s (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, 1960s-1980s (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Japanese Playboy Magazine, 1984 May (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, 1980s (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - Six audiocassettes, 1980s (Box 127, Folder 10-15)
    FILE CONTAINS AUDIO MATERIALS: Audio materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - Articles and clippings, 1980s (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Teru Kanazawa - KS book, 1985-1987 (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - NY Daily News - Natalie Byfield article, 1987 May 10 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - NY Post articles - PIP, 1982 (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Sankei articles, 1982 (Box 128, Folder 5-8)
  - KS articles and clippings, 1984 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Yomiuri Shimbun articles, 1984 March 1 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Decoration - Japanese Govt., 1968 (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Sekai Nippo correspondence, 1986 (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Yomiuri Shimbun articles, 1984 (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Sekai Nippo articles on KS, 1986 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Washington Post article PIP, 1982 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Sekai Nippo articles on KS and Dooman Group, 1986 August (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Appointment books, 1980-1988 (Box 130, Folder 1-7)
  - Address book, undated (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Appointment books, 1986, 1987, 1989 (Box 131, Folder 2-4)
  - Arlington - Kay Sugahara, 1988-1991 (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - Yankee Samurai typescript ch. 4, 1987 (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Memorial materials, 1988 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Address books, undated (Box 132, Folder 4-5)
  - Arlington materials, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - KS memorial articles, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Sendai reunion translation, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Photocopy of Dodo FDR bio, 1987 (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - Historical KS files, 1950-1988 (Box 133, Folder 5-19)
  - Japan trip scrapbook, 1960s (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - YS St. Croix & Hawaii photo album, 1985-1986 (Box 135, Folder 1)
  - Photo album, 1960s (Box 136, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 1940s-1980s (Box 137, Folder 1-5)
  - Save for archive letter, 2006 (Box 137, Folder 6)
  - Reagan letter to YS, 1988 (Box 137, Folder 7)
  - The Standard Star newspaper, 1958 (Box 137, Folder 8)
  - Olympic photo, 1995 January (Box 137, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, 1940s-1980s (Box 138, Folder 1)
  - Photo rolls, 1928, 1936 (Box 139, Folder 1-3)
  - Business cards collected by KS, undated (Box 139, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, 1940s-1980s (Box 140, Folder 1)
  - Seven VHS tapes, 1987-1994 (Box 141, Folder 1-7)
    FILE CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Audiovisual materials in this collection will require assessment and possible digitization for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
  - Three Betamax tapes, 1978 (Box 141, Folder 8-10)
  - Two DVD-Rs, 1987, 1994 (Box 141, Folder 11-12)
  - One Kay Sugahara Story CD-R, undated (Box 141, Folder 13)
  - One Souvenir Fairfield-Maxwell DVD, 2007 (Box 141, Folder 14)
  - FML 50th Anniversary files and & two DVDs, 2007-2008 (Box 142, Folder 1-9)
  - Family history files, 2005 (Box 142, Folder 10-25)
  - State and national archive files, 2005 (Box 143, Folder 1-9)
  - An Occupation Without Troops photocopy, 1996 (Box 143, Folder 10)
  - Kay Kuwahara interview, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 11-12)
  - Telegrams, letters, photographs and OSS service documents, 1940s-1950s (Box 143, Folder 13)
  - Bolton Priory clipping, 1966 (Box 143, Folder 14)
  - Misc. documents, 1943-1983 (Box 143, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence, 1946-1963 (Box 143, Folder 16-17)
  - G.S. documents and photos, 1948-1955 (Box 143, Folder 18)
  - Yankee Samurai manuscript by Kleiner, 1988 (Box 143, Folder 19)
  - Photographs and YS photo album, 1920s-1960s (Box 144, Folder 1)
  - YS photo albums, 1920s (Box 145, Folder 1)
  - Sugahara family scrapbook, 1950s (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Sugahara family photo album, 1970s (Box 146, Folder 2)
  - Shinbei Sugahara memorial photograph, undated (Box 146, Folder 3)
  - KS - UCLA diploma, 1932 (Box 147, Folder 1)
  - KS - FML scrapbooks, 1950s-1960s (Box 147, Folder 2-3)
  - Sugahara family photographs, 1920s-1950s (Box 148, Folder 1)
  - KS office and family photos, 1960s-1980s (Box 149, Folder 1)
  - Mt Fairchem Filly Launching Ceremony photo album, 2007 January 26 (Box 150, Folder 1)
  - Fumi Kuwahara folder, 1939 (Box 150, Folder 2)
  - Kay & Yone wedding portrait, undated (Box 150, Folder 3)
  - KS - Copies of Emperor's of Sacred Treasure award, 1968 (Box 150, Folder 4)
  - KS - historical files, 1940s-1950s (Box 151, Folder 1-11)
  - KS - historical file, 1940s-1950s (Box 152, Folder 1)
  - Nissho Maru launch photos, Sasebo Heavy Industries, 1962 July (Box 152, Folder 2)
  - Sunbelt Dixie slides, 1977 (Box 152, Folder 3)
  - GALI 30th Anniversary party photo album and CD-R, 2008 October 2 (Box 152, Folder 4)
  - KS curriculum vitae, 1955-1969 (Box 153, Folder 2)
  - KS personal old files, 1948-1963 (Box 153, Folder 3)
  - PR on KS - Leo Crowley, 1972 (Box 153, Folder 4)
  - Documents - KS - Dooman letter, 1950s-1980s (Box 153, Folder 5)
  - Casey/Howley, 1972-1973 (Box 153, Folder 6)
  - Ishii party correspondence, 1968 October 19 (Box 153, Folder 8)
  - Ishii visit, 1968 (Box 153, Folder 9)
  - Masa O'Connell - KS bio research, 1981 (Box 153, Folder 10-15)
  - Nakasone tribute to Nakabe published in memorial, 1978 (Box 154, Folder 1)
  - Doug Hamilton paper re: KS, 1982 October (Box 154, Folder 2)
  - KS - History of FMLTD, 1970s (Box 154, Folder 3-4)
  - Fairway Yen Bond - Tombstone file, 1972 (Box 154, Folder 5)
  - KS - bio, 1982 March (Box 154, Folder 6)
  - Playboy Japan KS interview, 1984 May (Box 154, Folder 7-8)
  - Professional translation of Sankei articles, 1982 (Box 154, Folder 9)
  - Esquire article on KS, 1972 (Box 154, Folder 10)
  - Japanese award offered to KS, 1986 (Box 154, Folder 11)
  - Okura Lantern magazine, 1973 (Box 154, Folder 12)
  - Photos Dinner for Frank Fahrenkopf, 1986 (Box 155, Folder 1)
  - Marion launch photos, 1950s-1970 (Box 155, Folder 2-4)
  - Map of Japan with KS notes, undated (Box 155, Folder 5)
  - Photo index, 1980s (Box 155, Folder 6)
  - Mondale dinner photos, Hotel Okura, Tokyo, 1981 November 26 (Box 155, Folder 7)
  - Meeting with Gov. Graham FL. - KS, BTS, US Asia Institute photos, 1982 (Box 155, Folder 8)
  - PIP press coverage, 1981-1984 (Box 155, Folder 9-10)
  - Photos from white album, 1980s (Box 155, Folder 11)
  - Photos - KS/Paul Japan trip, 1977 May (Box 155, Folder 12)
  - USAI scrapbook, 1982 (Box 155, Folder 13)
  - Red photo album, 1980 (Box 156, Folder 1)
  - KS - wallets & card cases, undated (Box 159, Folder 6)
  - Account notebook & notes, 1930s-1940s (Box 159, Folder 7)
  - HS graduation clipping and notebooks, 1950s (Box 159, Folder 8)
  - Happy Sprite reception book - Japanese, 1980 (Box 160, Folder 1)
  - Fairfield - Christened photo album, 1972 March 24 (Box 160, Folder 2)
  - Post-Board Meeting dinner, Bermuda and ship album, 1968-1984 (Box 161, Folder 1)
  - Fairfield - Delivered photo album, 1972 (Box 161, Folder 2)
  - Sunbelt Dixie scrapbook, 1978 (Box 162, Folder 1)
  - Sunbelt Dixie photo album, 1978 (Box 162, Folder 2)
  - Black leather photo album 1, 1960-1971 (Box 163, Folder 1)
  - Alaska Rex photo album, 1983 (Box 163, Folder 2)
  - Black leather photo album 2, 1940s-1980s (Box 164, Folder 1)
  - Happy Sprite photo album, 1983 (Box 164, Folder 2)
  - Magellan Rex photo album, 1984 (Box 165, Folder 1)
  - Fairfield Jason photo album, 1974 (Box 165, Folder 2)
  - Keiyo Maru photo album, 1983 (Box 166, Folder 1)
  - Oyashio Rex photo album, 1984 (Box 166, Folder 2)